outofprintclothing.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy — Out of Print

**This Privacy Policy is effective as of  September 1, 2017.**

Welcome to the website of Out of Print. Sputnik 84, LLC (d/b/a Out of Print) ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.outofprintclothing.com (the "Site" or "Website"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

**Information We Collect**

We automatically collect your IP address, but not your email address, when you visit our Site. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. We may use cookies, web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels") and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you interact with our websites or emails, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior. We may combine this information with other information we collect about you and use it for various purposes, such as improving our websites and your online experience, understanding which areas and features of our sites are popular, counting visits, understanding campaign effectiveness, tailoring our communications with you, determining whether an email has been opened and links within the email have been clicked and for other internal business purposes. Only anonymous, aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. We collect your contact information (like email address) and financial information (like credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to you. Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for products and services. We use your mailing address to ship your products to you, and to verify your billing information. Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from our Site will allow you to unsubscribe and opt out of future mailings.

We may share your Personal Information with third parties (i) who need your information to provide services to us, and (ii) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or property, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government, judicial or other legal request, or to comply with the law.  We may also share your Personal Information with third parties for third party marketing purposes unless you elect for us not to do so by emailing us with your name and address at optout@outofprintclothing.com.

_Cookies_

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled. It may affect the user experience and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting our customer service number at 1-844-667-7468.

_Online Behavioral Advertising_

We may partner with third party ad network(s) to either display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other websites. Our ad network partner(s) may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on our Website and other websites to provide you with targeted advertising based upon your interests.

**Information Use**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

**Security**

We use SSL encryption and other methods to secure your data. The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Change of Control**

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Site. We may also sell certain assets associated with the Site. As a result, please be aware that in such event we may transfer some or all of your information to a company acquiring us or all or part of our assets or to another company with which we have merged. Under such circumstances we would, to the extent possible, require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. Nevertheless, we cannot ensure that an acquiring company or the merged company will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Privacy Policy. ** **

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you are under the age of thirteen (13) you should not register, order, purchase or provide information to or from Out of Print.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that we may revise this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. When we do, we will post the change(s) on this page. In the event that we make any material change(s), we will provide appropriate notice to you. We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Policy for any updates and/or changes. The date this page was last revised is displayed at the top of this page. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at help@outofprintclothing.com or by mail:

Out of Print  
127 West 26th Street, Suite 400  
New York, NY 10001
